I remember when I was little and then we had cash-
-And I saved them in my piggy bank and sometimes I took out my money and put them on the floor.
Then I wrote on a paper how much I had saved.
My first goal was to save for a Sony Ericsson mobile phone.
I very much wanted to have it, so I saved as much as I could-
-To be able to afford to buy this mobile.
And it's always followed with me.
This to save for something-
-or just that it's fun to feel that you have money.
I started investing by reading a lot, I googled a lot and then I opened an account at Avanza.
Then I was 19 years old, so it's just over 7 years ago.
So 7 years ago, in 2013 I think, then I bought Avanza Zero for SEK 2,500.
Well, I have 4 companies in my equity portfolio today.
Some may think that is a little higher risk, but I like it to be high risk.
And I like when it swings a lot.
I think it's fun.
Today it is Castellum, Mycronic, Sinch and Plejd.
Then I also have 7 funds and you can see them here.
Gabbe Lönn Erlandsson.
Do you have any example of places you can invest in the interest-on-interest effect to secure their future savings?
Earn Gabbe
I don't really know what you mean, but interest on the interest effect you achieve if it is that you invest in anything-
-And then you get a return or interest rate and then reinvest it.
So that the following year or a while thereafter, you get a greater return or a greater interest rate.
It is therefore believed that the investment will go down.
This can be done with leverage products such as Bull, Bear, Turbovarians, CFDS.
There are a variety of such products.
In fact, I do not know all these products in my head, but leverage products are not recommended for beginners.
It's pretty easy to burn there.
If you want to count on the risks with a leverage, then you will have to look at how much leverage it is in the product that you buy.
Then you get to look at the potential tender side, if it is so that it would go down 5 %-
-Multiply it with the leverage, type.
There you have your risk.
Plus any fees and interest rates for that product.
It is a very complicated question that is very difficult to go into right now.
The risk is great when you shop with leverage, so read on properly and make sure you learn first.
Tore Landin Larsson.
My real brother, the star.
Strategies for purchases, sales, reallocation.
It would be interesting how you reason about it.
So, when you take home profits, selling poor holdings, if you are long on minus placements or if you sell them with the highest development?
Well, it's a little hard to say something that is red.
If it is so that I see that a company does not develop as well as I hope-
Why should you join a sinking ship for?
Then it is better that you get rid of that leaven.
That's usually how I think.
Then I would rather jump on a boat or train that goes and where the chance to make money is greater.
I also invest my money in something that I feel can give me more value for my investment.
Than I should have them in any sourdough that does not give me a return simply.
Tony Godlike Lindh.
Is it better to distribute the same amount to funds or a large amount on a single fund?
Yes, you Tony.
It is a good question I would rather make myself so that I spread the amount among different funds.
Some funds that I think will go better I have slightly larger amounts in.
And some others have a little less amount in which I may think is high risk and other things.